http://www.airways.co.nz/privacy-policy/

Back
AirBooks library: Introduction to ATC (for non-controllers)
AirBooks libraries
AirBooks library: Introduction to ATC (for non-controllers)
Privacy statement
This privacy statement explains how Airways Corporation New Zealand Limited (“Airways”) collects, stores and uses your personal information.Openness and transparency are important to us. The Privacy Act 2020 requires us – like any other New Zealand agency – to tell you certain things about the personal information we need in order to carry out our functions.As we take our obligations under The Privacy Act 2020 seriously, we would like to explain what personal information we collect and how we use or share it. We will also explain about the way we store and protect personal information, your rights to access and correct it and how our website processes personal information.Our Privacy ObligationsWe only collect personal information where it is necessary in order to carry out our functions, which may include security validation that we use to protect you and Airways from malicious actors or malware.We may collect personal information about you either directly from you or from other people or agencies, and we may generate personal information about you when we carry out our functions.We store all our data (including ur personal information) in secured facilities that are protected with all reasonable technical and process controls appropriate to the data being stored (more information on this below under “Storage and Website Use”).You can ask us for a copy of your personal information at any time. We will be as open as we can with you and ensure that we meet our obligationsWe will only use and share personal information where necessary to carry out the functions for which we collected it, or if required to do so by law.If you cannot find the information you need, or you have concerns about the way we are managing your personal information, then please contact us at any time by emailing info@airways.co.nzWe may update this privacy statement from time to time, for example to reflect changes to the Privacy Act, so feel free to check in again occasionally to see what might have changed. This statement was last updated in December 2020.How we Collect, Use and Store Personal InformationCollection:Most of the personal information we collect is provided directly by you, or your authorised representative, when you engage with us.You do not have to provide your personal information to us. However, we may not be able to effectively provide you with services if you do not provide us with the information we need.The personal information we may collect from you directly can include:
your name
your contact details, including your address, email address or phone number
information about your authorised representative (if you have one)
any documents or other information you provide to us in order to receive our services
correspondence from you sent to us, and
Data that we use to assess the security of the transaction with you such as the operating system you use, type of browser and similar information that allows us to protect you and Airways.
In the course of providing you with services we may generate personal information about you. The personal information we may generate about you includes:
correspondence (such as letters and emails), including between our staff or with the staff of other agencies
file notes, memoranda, meeting minutes or other records of actions taken, and
legal views or opinions.
UseWe collect personal information in order to provide our products or services or answer queries. We may engage specialist third party data processors to assist us to deliver products and services including security assessments.  You may request a list of our current third party data processors from us at any time at the contact details below. We may share all or some of your information with our related companies.  Airways Corporation of New Zealand Limited represents a group of companies, and we may share your information internally where required to provide you products and services. For example, some of our accounts and billing is provided for us by another Airways company. We have robust internal processes in place to ensure that any of your information shared with our related companies is protected to the same standard we use for our own information. Airways uses cloud based technology and for its own use relies on data centres that are primarily based in Azure and primarily located in Australia. However, some services may house data in other jurisdictions or may be in-house within Airways own data centres. Airways assess the security and appropriateness of all off-shore data facilities through the DIA105 guidelines which are available through the Department of Internal Affairs.Because some of our data is stored offshore, we will make every endeavour to not transfer your personal information overseas without either first ensuring that the transfer and recipient country comply with the requirements of the Privacy Act 2020 and/or first notifying you.Storage and Website UseWhen you use our website, you may provide various personal details such as your name and email address. This information, and any other information provided by you or collected/generated by us may be used by us so that we can communicate with you and provide secure services to you. In addition to the details you provide, the server (including those of its web host specified below) will record the specific transactions you perform when visiting this website. This information will primarily be used for statistical purposes but also to ensure on-going security.Web server logs are also kept for the purposes of generating site usage statistics and performing security auditing. The logs record information every time you request a page from the server. This information will not be used to identify you except in the event of irregularities in the use of the site. The information logged may include:
The time of each page request
The pages you requested
What web browser you are using
Your client IP address
What site you came to this website from, and
Other security specific data we need to ensure the on-going security of the transactions with you and others who use our site.
The web host for this website (excluding online purchasing) is the New Zealand Government Common Web Platform. You may contact us at the email address specified below for further details of the web host.CookiesCookies are small pieces of information that a website can store on your computer through your web browser. This website uses cookies only for maintaining your user session – the cookies will not be stored to your hard disk.In order to use this Website, your browser must be configured to accept cookies. You can usually configure your browser to warn you before accepting cookies if you wish.SecurityYour user details and password are stored in a secure database with your password being hashed before being stored. Whenever your user details or password are transmitted between the server and your browser, the details are transmitted over Secure Sockets Layer (SSL).AccessYou have the right to ask for a copy of any personal information we hold about you, and to ask for it to be corrected if you think it is wrong. If you’d like to ask for a copy of your information, or to have it corrected, please contact us at info@airways.co.nzYour privacy rights and how to contact usShould you have an enquiry relating to this privacy statement or any privacy related concern, please email info@airways.co.nz.
Get notified when a new vacancy is added
Subscribe
Need to know morefrom us?
Contact Us
Terms of use
Privacy statement
Copyright 2020 Airways
